{
    
        "ChanDingYin": {
            "answers": [
                {
                  "question": "What is the 'ChanDingYin' hand gesture also known as?",
                  "correct_option": "Dharmadhatu Mudra"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which hand is placed on top in the 'ChanDingYin' hand gesture?",
                  "correct_option": "Right hand"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What does the 'ChanDingYin' hand gesture symbolize?",
                  "correct_option": "Inner peace and meditation"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which Buddha is associated with the 'ChanDingYin' hand gesture?",
                  "correct_option": "Vairocana (Mahavairocana)"
                }
              ]
              
        },
        "HuoYanYin": {
            "answers": [
                {
                  "question": "Which group of deities does the 'HuoYanYin' hand gesture belong to?",
                  "correct_option": "Mingwang (Wrathful Kings)"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Who is the main deity associated with the 'HuoYanYin' hand gesture?",
                  "correct_option": "Acalinatha (Fudo Myo-o)"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What does the 'HuoYanYin' hand gesture symbolize?",
                  "correct_option": "Compassion and protection"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is a unique feature of the 'HuoYanYin' hand gesture?",
                  "correct_option": "Thumb presses against the back of three fingers"
                }
              ]
        },
        "MiTuoDingYin": {
            "answers": [
                {
                  "question": "What does the 'MiTuoDingYin' hand gesture symbolize?",
                  "correct_option": "The manifestation of the four wisdoms of Bodhi"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which fingers are crossed in the 'MiTuoDingYin' hand gesture?",
                  "correct_option": "Little, ring, and middle fingers"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which Buddha uses the 'MiTuoDingYin' hand gesture?",
                  "correct_option": "Amitabha (Amida)"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is another name for the 'MiTuoDingYin' hand gesture?",
                  "correct_option": "Wondrous Observing Wisdom Mudra"
                }
              ]
              
        },
        "Retsu": {
            "answers": [
                {
                  "question": "What does the 'Retsu' hand gesture symbolize?",
                  "correct_option": "Time and space control, representing the heart to help others"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which Buddha is associated with the 'Retsu' hand gesture?",
                  "correct_option": "Vairocana (Mahavairocana)"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How is the 'Retsu' hand gesture performed?",
                  "correct_option": "Both hands form vajra fists, left index finger points up, right little finger wraps around left index finger"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is another name for the 'Retsu' hand gesture?",
                  "correct_option": "Great Wisdom Fist Mudra"
                }
              ]
              
        },
        "Rin": {
            "answers": [
                {
                  "question": "What does the 'Rin' hand gesture symbolize?",
                  "correct_option": "Stability of body and mind, representing an unwavering will"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the name of the mudra (hand gesture) associated with 'Rin'?",
                  "correct_option": "Immovable Wisdom King Mudra"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which mantra is associated with the 'Rin' hand gesture?",
                  "correct_option": "Heart Mantra of Vajrasattva"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What does the 'Rin' hand gesture help achieve?",
                  "correct_option": "Stability and unwavering determination"
                }
              ]
              
        },
        "TaiJiYin": {
            "answers": [
                {
                  "question": "How is the 'TaiJiYin' hand gesture performed?",
                  "correct_option": "Left hand on the outside, right hand on the inside, both palms facing inward"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which fingers are involved in forming the 'TaiJiYin' hand gesture?",
                  "correct_option": "Left thumb pinching left middle finger tip, right thumb pinching left ring finger root"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What does the 'TaiJiYin' hand gesture symbolize?",
                  "correct_option": "Union of Yin and Yang"
                },
                {
                  "question": "In the 'TaiJiYin' hand gesture, what does the position of the right hand represent?",
                  "correct_option": "Yang embracing Yin"
                }
              ]
              
        },
        "Zai": {
            "answers": [
                {
                  "question": "What does the 'Zai' hand gesture symbolize?",
                  "correct_option": "Control of the five elements, representing the free use of supernatural abilities"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the name of the mudra (hand gesture) associated with 'Zai'?",
                  "correct_option": "Sun Wheel Mudra"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which mantra is associated with the 'Zai' hand gesture?",
                  "correct_option": "Heart Mantra of Vairocana (Mahavairocana)"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What ability does the 'Zai' hand gesture enhance?",
                  "correct_option": "The free use of supernatural abilities"
                }
              ]
              
        },
        "Zen": {
            "answers": [
                {
                  "question": "What does the 'Zen' hand gesture symbolize?",
                  "correct_option": "Telepathy and invisibility, representing the ability to gather wealth and love"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What is the name of the mudra (hand gesture) associated with 'Zen'?",
                  "correct_option": "Inner Binding Mudra"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which mantra is associated with the 'Zen' hand gesture?",
                  "correct_option": "Six-Syllable Vajra Mantra of Padmasambhava"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What abilities does the 'Zen' hand gesture enhance?",
                  "correct_option": "Telepathy and invisibility"
                }
              ]
              
        },
        "ZhiJiXiangYin": {
            "answers": [
                {
                  "question": "How is the 'ZhiJiXiangYin' hand gesture performed?",
                  "correct_option": "Both hands each place the thumb under the middle finger, other fingers extended, left hand in front of the chest, right hand above but not touching"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What does the 'ZhiJiXiangYin' hand gesture symbolize?",
                  "correct_option": "Bestowing wisdom and good fortune"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Which Buddha's fundamental mudra is the 'ZhiJiXiangYin' hand gesture?",
                  "correct_option": "Vairocana (Mahavairocana)"
                },
                {
                  "question": "What variation is used for the Dharmakaya (Truth Body) preaching mudra?",
                  "correct_option": "Thumb under the ring finger"
                }
              ]
              
        }
    
}
